let me say this we don't really know each other as a global african i can tell you for most kenyans
don't know nothing about ugandans most kenyans don't know nothing about ethiopias and ethiopians
we share the same border most kenyans know nothing about somalia and we share the same
border with somalia why is that because at the end of the day we we are we have been mentally
politically economically socially programmed to operate in these berlin conferences
i have a whole song about that syop syops it's all the syop can't believe nothing
because they stay front and they didn't lie to you that's what syop is about
they is them and who they are is not what you think it's really just the song is really asking
you to ask yourself what is my perception of the world and who shaped it
and when you ask yourself that you realize i didn't shape it so then how do i start shaping
my perception of the world so for every kenyan that doesn't know anything about uganda about
somalia about ethiopia you have to ask yourself why don't i know anything about somalia uganda and
ethiopia whose decision was that because i was made to go to school for all these years
and it wasn't my decision to go to school so i was in a school that decisively did not teach me
about the people around me why because were the were africa to be united it would not be able to be
exploited that is why because if you know about somalia and you know about ethiopia and you know
about uganda then you're gonna care about ethiopia and you're gonna care about somalia and you're
gonna care about uganda and if you care about them and they care about you then now you have an
alliance and you cannot be as easily exploited and the great example of this is what's happening in
this is what's happening in the sighel yeah